遠鑒字幕組&彎彎字幕組聯合制作
[Visionary] 0day-sub
翻譯         波伏瓦瓦 Ash 布布 contessina Christina
翻譯         邇燚 發條橘子 Hephaestus 海魚 黑色曼陀羅
翻譯         immortals Peter Jettatore suttree 自由 VIPHD
翻譯          小果凍 伊馮波波娜 彩虹仔 石碎 阿奇德菲哥哥
翻譯          樂天 二凡 胡蘿蔔難吃 Nope Keys
校對         西木 布布 william2568
熱門電影字幕歡迎關注微博 @遠鑒字幕組v
若是想施展您的翻譯才華 讓自己的名字出現在字幕開頭
遠鑒字幕組歡迎您加入 遠鑒字幕組招新群 483552098
彎彎字幕組招新群 562846983
招募各語種翻譯 誠邀您的加入
觀眾您好
如果給您分發的資源的人未明確指出是遠鑒字幕組作品
或是裁剪\去除掉了片頭的字幕組製作人資訊
說明您可能獲取的是二手資源
獲取一手資源 拒絕二手資源 從您做起
更多精彩內容 敬請關注微博 @遠鑒字幕組v
皇家酒店謀殺案
十年後
你迷路了嗎 神父
Are you lost, Father?
你說什麼
Sorry?
我說你迷路了嗎
Are you lost?
沒有
No.
我應該沒有迷路
I suppose not.
這上面說 我現在在內華達
According to this, I am in Nevada.
內華達
這是我第一次來內華達
I've never been to Nevada before.
這兒怎麼樣
What's it like?
還可以吧
Oh... It's not bad.
看樣子可能要下雨了
Looks like it might rain.
加州最近怎麼樣
What's California like these days?
這個嘛...
Well...
一直陽光明媚
still sunny.
我幫你拿吧
Can I give you a hand there?
你人真好
That's very kind of you.
謝謝
Thank you.
哎呀
Oh!
請
Please.
到目前為止 你覺得內達華怎麼樣
How are you enjoying Nevada so far?
目前來說 一切都好
So far, so good.
那邊是我的行李
Those are my accouterments.
前臺那兒那些
Over there by the front desk.
我的箱子 裡面有我能穿兩周的衣服
That's my trunk. That's my fortnighter.
還有我裝帽子的箱子
That's my hat case.
我想請你們這幫人...
And I would ask you folk...
在分房的時候
to please respect my claim
能尊重一下我的意見
when it comes time to divvyin' up the rooms.
雖然到底什麼時候分房 誰也說不準
But when that'll be is anybody's guess.
剛剛我一直在按那該死的鈴 按得我手酸
Been ringin' that dang bell so much my hand is tired.
耳朵也疼
My ears are sore.
我現在需要咖啡來補充點體能
And my constitution needs coffee.
所以我才在這吧台這後面翻一翻看看能有什麼
That's why I was scratchin' around back there.
還真找到了一些咖啡...
I did find some...
但我可不敢保證它的品質
though I can't vouch for the quality.
我是拉勒米·西摩·蘇利文
Laramie Seymour Sullivan.
卡爾霍恩電器的銷售經理
Sales manager, Calhoun Appliances.
我的名字可能上不了這兒的頭版頭條
My name might not be on the masthead there...
卡爾霍恩電器
但我們公司是一個不錯的家族企業
but that don't mean we aren't a family business.
-女士  -您好
- Ma'am.  - Hello.
我該怎麼稱呼您呢 神父
And what may I call you, Father?
丹尼爾·弗林 很高興見到你
Daniel Flynn. Nice to meet you.
弗林神父 這個稱呼很好記
Oh, Father Flynn. That's easy to remember.
很押韻
Alliterative and such.
您是在哪個教區工作呢
Whereabouts is your parish?
印第安那州布隆明頓市的聖母無玷聖心書院
The Immaculate Heart of Mary's in Bloomington, Indiana.
那首先我要代表我自己
Well, let me just say up front that myself
和東比洛西克浸信會的善男信女說一句...
and the good people of East Biloxi Baptist...
我們也許和你們的教皇有分歧...
may have our differences with your pope...
但我相信我們每個人內心
but I do believe we all carry
都承載著耶穌基督的神性
the divinity of Jesus Christ in our hearts.
在我看來 這就能使我們也能成為兄弟
And that makes us brothers as far as I'm concerned.
如果您願意的話 我非常希望您能去
You're more than welcome to give that bell a whirl
按一下鈴
if you'd like.
您的運氣可能比我好
You might have better luck than I did.
你是做什麼的 親愛的
So what about you, darlin'?
你是做酒店生意的嗎
Are you in the hospitality business?
不 我不在酒店行業工作
I do not work in the hospitality business, no.
不論如何 我還是要把名片給你
Well, I am going to give you my card anyway.
我猜你肯定認識些 需要吸塵器的姑娘
I bet you know some gals who just might need a vacuum.
你們第一次住皇家酒店嗎
Your first time at the El Royale?
這裡以前不是這樣的
Well, it wasn't always like this.
我不只是說
And I don't just mean
以前你起碼能找到個接待員來給你登記入住
you could find a clerk come check-in time.
不只這樣
No, no, no.
這個酒店 曾熙熙攘攘
This place used to be hustlin' and bustlin'.
是太浩湖不能說的的秘密
Tahoe's best-kept secret.
這兒總有一些新奇的東西
I mean it was always a bit of a novelty,
當然了
yeah, sure, of course.
像是州辦的集會啊
But there's state fair novelty
還有像是賽馬的地方
and then there's old horse novelty.
我相信我們肯定是喜歡賽馬那一類型的
And I believe we are firmly in the old horse variety.
就是這樣 先生 這酒店在1966年的時候可火了
Yes sir! 1966, this place had swing.
我甚至都未曾想過 我能在這的主樓
Hell, I don't even think I could get a room here
搞到一間房
in the main lodge if I tried.
這裡是太浩湖人的藏身之處 你懂我的意思嗎
It was a hidey-hole for the Tahoe swells, you know?
迪恩·馬丁還在一首歌中唱到了
Old Dean Martin even sang a song about it.
"想念在加利福尼亞和裘蒂在一起的日子"
"Half in California with Judy."
沒聽過嗎
No?
不過這確實不是他最經典的曲目 喝咖啡嗎
Well, wasn't one of his best. Coffee?
-不用了 謝了  -喝點吧 別不好意思
- Oh, no, thank you.  Oh, come on, girl.
我可煮了一壺 別浪費了呀
I made a whole pot. Shame for it to go to waste.
給你倒上
There you go.
好姑娘
Atta girl.
我一會兒讓接待員說給你聽他的那一套介紹
I'll let the clerk give you the whole spiel
如果他還會出來的話
if he ever shows up again, that is.
但他們總會忘了講
But the thing they always leave out...
這家酒店失去博彩許可證的事
is that this place lost its gambling license
大概就在一年前
about a year ago.
好像是委員會還是誰幹的
Something to do with the commission or some such.
他們內心膨脹起來 就不在這兒做生意了
So all the swells took their business elsewhere.
現在整個主樓都對外開放
Now the main lodge is all that's open.
泳池裡都是鴨子
The pool is filled with ducks.
他們甚至還做鐘點房的生意
And they'll even rent you a room by the hour
如果你需要安靜
if you ask real quietlike.
-給你 神父  -謝謝
- There you go, Father.  - Thank you.
不客氣 不過 說實話
Mmm-hmm. Although if we're bein' honest...
我們在這裡的唯一原因
that's probably the only reason that a priest,
一位神父 一位吸塵器推銷員和一個黑妞
a vacuum salesman, and a negro...
是因為我們只能承擔這兒的費用 不是嗎
could afford freight here, am I right?
開個玩笑
I'm just funnin'.
老實說 我在卡爾霍恩電器住的房間
Truth be told, my stay is on Calhoun Appliances...
讓我覺得選擇一個好的房間 是多麼的重要
which is why room choice is so important to me...
也讓我希望 人們因為我的穿著而尊重我
and why I ask you to respect my accoutrement
對我來講 這些就是我的名片
as proxy to my person.
我想要犒勞自己
I intend to lavish myself.
所以我總想住蜜月套房
I always wanted to stay in the honeymoon suite...
雖然我沒在度蜜月
although I'm not currently on my honeymoon.
神父阿 這女人手段可比我們要強硬
The lady's got a harder hand than we do, Father.
天
Oh...
抱歉讓你們久等了
I am very sorry to keep you waiting.
該死 小夥子你去哪了
Damn, boy, where you been?
我在這大廳裡等得鬍子都長出來了
Waitin' in this lobby so long, I could use a shave.
你為什麼才出現
What's wrong with you?
實在是抱歉
I am very sorry.
您在這裡做什麼 神父先生
What are you doing here, Father?
我認識你嗎 孩子
Do I know you, son?
不認識 但我的意思是 這不是神父該來的地方 先生
No. But, I mean, this is not a place for a priest, Father.
你不應該來這兒
You shouldn't be here.
你真的得好好學一下銷售話術了 孩子
We might need to work on your sales pitch, son.
“皇家大酒店 不對神父開放”
"The El Royale, no place for a priest."
還有很多別的旅館 神父先生
There are other hotels, Father.
估計離太浩湖更近一些 我可以幫您找一間
Maybe closer to Tahoe. I could help you find one.
我保證您會更喜歡那邊的
I'm sure you would be happier there.
-米爾斯 是嗎  -是的
- Uh, Miles, is it?  - Mmm-hmm.
米爾斯 如果這裡不是一個神父該來的地方
If this is not a place for a priest, Miles...
那這就恰恰是主想讓我來的地方
then this is exactly where the Lord wants me.
不過 主是不會在蜜月套房召喚你的
Well, the Lord don't want you in the honeymoon suite.
這點我可以保證
I can promise you that.
米爾斯 我的行李在那兒
Miles, those are my accoutrement there
給我留個房間
and I stake my claim as such.
你可以先給他們辦入住
But you can go ahead and check them in first.
我不著急
I don't mind.
沒事的 孩子
It's all right, son.
快 孩子
Come on, boy.
讓他聽聽你那套說辭
Give him the whole spiel.
皇家大酒店 什麼什麼的
The El Royale. And blah, blah, blah.
皇家大酒店是位於兩州交界的一處住所
The El Royale is a bi-state establishment.
您可以選擇住在
You have the option to stay
加利福尼亞州
in either the great state of California...
或者是內華達州
or the great state of Nevada.
享受西部溫暖的氣候和明媚的陽光
Warmth and sunshine to the west...
或感受東部的機遇與希望
or hope and opportunity to the east.
您更喜歡哪一邊
Which would you prefer?
有什麼區別嗎
What's the difference?
您是指加利福尼亞州和內達華州嗎
Between California and Nevada?
我是說房間之間
Between the rooms.
這個嘛 對於第一次入住的人
Well, for starters,
加利福尼亞州的房間價錢要高出1美元
rooms in California cost a dollar more.
是嗎 什麼時候的事
Really? When did that happen?
那邊的房間好在哪裡
What makes 'em a dollar better?
它們位於加利福尼亞州
They're in California.
就這樣? 這有值1美元嗎
And that's worth a dollar?
有些人是這麼認為的
Some people think so.
你有這些人的電話嗎
You got a phone number for any of those people?
我想賣幾台吸塵器
'Cause I sure would like to sell them
給他們
one of these vacuum cleaners.
對了 說到這
Hey, speaking of which,
你們酒店裡誰負責接待
who handles your hospitality here at the hotel?
目前來說 還是我
Currently, that is also me.
喔 這就...
Oh, well...
操蛋了
Shit.
一會再說這個吧
We'll have to worry about that later.
我能看一下你們酒店的佈局圖嗎
May I see a map of the hotel, please?
可以
Mmm-hmm.
淡季的時候只有主樓是可以住的
Only the main lodge is available in the off-season.
你可以使用加利福尼亞區的娛樂設施
You could still use the California amenities
即使你選擇住在內華達區
if you choose to stay in Nevada.
加州區的娛樂資源是什麼
What exactly is a California amenity?
比如說
Uh, for instance,
在內華達州是不允許售賣酒品的
we're not allowed to sell liquor in Nevada.
所以要是我們想喝酒的話
So if we wanna drink,
就必須去那邊的房間嗎
we gotta do it on that side of the room?
是的 先生
That is correct, sir.
另外 一杯咖啡25美分
Also, coffee is 25 cents a cup.
讓我猜猜 你還做酒保是嗎
Let me guess. You're also the bartender?
是的 先生
That is correct, sir.
好吧...
All right. Well...
給你 用來擲硬幣
Feel free to flip that
如果你不知道怎麼選的話 神父
if you need to make a decision, Father.
光在這個地方等著就開始花錢了
Startin' to cost me money waitin' around this place.
四 我要四號房間
Four. I'll take room four.
您需要先付一個晚上的錢 八美元
I'll need one night in advance. Eight dollars.
還有25美分的咖啡錢
And it's 25 cents for the coffee.
請簽一下帳單
Please sign the ledger.
神父 丹尼爾 弗林
下一位
Who's next?
能給我一個在內華達區的房間嗎 米爾斯
May I have a room in Nevada please, Miles?
五號房間
Room five.
還有別的空房間嗎
Um, is there another room available?
稍微遠一些的
Possibly further away?
這個嘛...那些房間沒人打掃過 不適合居住
Uh, those rooms have not been serviced and are unsuitable.
清潔員的活也是他一個人幹 記得嗎
He also does the housekeeping, remember?
加州區還有空房 女士
There are rooms in California available, ma'am.
米爾斯 她是不想挨著神父
Miles, she don't wanna be near the priest.
我們又不是沒看見她走進這裡
It's not like we didn't see her walkin' in here...
胳膊下麵夾著她的鋪蓋捲兒
with her own bed rolls under her arms.
我不是對你有意見 親愛的
No judgment on you there, darlin'.
也許你可以在這兒和神父談談...
Maybe you can talk to the Father here...
關於瑪利亞·抹大拉以及寬恕之類的
about, uh, Mary Magdalene and forgiveness and whatnot.
那就五號房間吧
Room five will be fine.
請簽一下帳單
Please sign the ledger.
還有25美分的咖啡錢
And it's 25 cents for the coffee.
好 當然
Okay. Of course.
謝謝
Thank you.
達琳 斯維特
我幫你把行李搬到房間吧
Can I give you a hand to your room?
不用
No.
對不起 神父
Sorry, Father. Uh...
你人很好 但我自己能行
That's very kind of you. But I can manage from here.
女士
Ma'am.
下午好
Good afternoon.
下一位
Who's next?
請吧 你先去辦理
Please, be my fuckin' guest.
我要一個房間
I need a room.
皇家酒店位於兩個州的交界處
The El Royale is a bi-state establishment.
你可以選擇住在這邊的...
You have the option to stay in either the great state of...
我要這間
I'll take this one.
這個...
Um...
想都別想
Don't fuckin' tell me.
我要一號房間
I'll take room one.
一號房間是我的
You can't have room one.
你沒有看到我的行李箱就在你腳下嗎
Do you not see my fortnighter right there at your feet?
我真的得再
Do I really have to explain
給這個該死的嬉皮士解釋一遍我們是自由選房
the concept of a free-market claim stake...
先到先得嗎
to the goddamn hippie?
那隨便給我一間這邊的房間吧
Give me something along this wall then.
這邊的空房
The available rooms on that wall
還沒有清理呢 另外
have yet to be cleaned, and...
無所謂 多少錢
I don't give a shit. How much?
8美元
Eight dollars.
麻煩簽一下帳單
Please sign the ledger.
入住愉快啦 女士
You have yourself a pleasant day, ma'am.
不錯嘛
Nice.
去你媽的
我要一號房
I'll take room one.
一號房
喂 親愛的 對不起
Hello, my love. I'm sorry.
我知道
I know.
我沒想到入住手續辦了這麼久
Check-in took a little longer than expected.
她睡了沒
Is she still up?
好
Good.
喂 小兔兔
Hello, bunny rabbit.
是的
Yes.
時間是對的 爸爸錯了
The clock is right and Daddy is wrong.
對不起 我晚了
I'm sorry. I was delayed.
我準備好了
I am ready.
是的 已經跪下了
Yes, I am on my knees.
現在我躺下進入睡眠
Now I lay me down to sleep...
原主保佑我
pray the Lord my soul to keep.
如果我在睡夢中死去...
If I should die before I wake...
我們不說這一段了嗎
We're not saying that part anymore?
你從哪裡聽到"變態"這個詞的
Where did you hear the word "morbid"?
那媽媽想我們說什麼
Well, what does Mommy want us to say?
說“當我們早上起床時”嗎 好的
"And when I wake in the morning light"? Okay.
當我們早上...
And when I wake in the...
從頭來嗎
From the beginning?
好的
Okay.
現在我躺下進入睡眠
Now I lay me down to sleep...
原主保佑我
I pray the Lord my soul to keep.
當我早上起床時...
And when I wake in the morning light...
引導我做對的事
teach me to do what's right.
阿門
Amen.
好啦 小兔兔 爸爸要掛電話啦
Okay, bunny rabbit, Daddy has to go.
告訴媽媽我愛她好嗎
Will you tell Mommy I love her?
還有 我也愛你 晚安啦
And I love you, too. Sleep tight.
我們聯合起來 能為和平做出一點貢獻
Together can serve the cause of peace.
總統先生 您認為我們可能
Mr. President, do you consider it possible
會和越南休戰嗎
to have a ceasefire in Vietnam...
在越南領土還是由越共統領的時候
so long as the Viet Cong still occupy Vietnamese territory?
我認為這個時候 用"休戰"這個詞...
I think that it is not helpful in discussing Vietnam...
沒有什麼意義
to use such terms as "ceasefire"...
因為休戰這個術語
because ceasefire is a term of art...
和他們打的遊擊戰
that really has no relevance,
沒有任何關係
in my opinion, to a guerrilla war.
當我們談論常規戰爭時
When you're talking about a conventional war...
休戰 是指雙方達成協議
then a ceasefire, agreed upon by two parties,
停止攻擊對方
means that the shooting stops.
但打遊擊戰的時候
But when you have a guerrilla war in which
其中一方可能根本沒法控制
one side may not even be able to control...
那些該為當地戰爭
many of those who are responsible
責任的人...
for the violence in the area...
談論休戰是沒意義的
the ceasefire may be meaningless.
以上是7頻道 特別新聞報導
This is a Channel 7 News Special Report.
警方正在搜查嫌疑人
Police are searching for suspects
在這場可怕的謀殺案中
in the grisly murders...
馬里布縣的有名的兒科醫生
of noted Malibu County pediatrician
伯納德·韋伯和他的妻子艾絲琳
Bernard Webber and his wife, Etheline.
於今日清晨
The couple was found stabbed to death
在他們濱海區的家中被殺害
early this morning in their beachfront home.
請接長官辦公室 案件246673
Director's office. Case 246673.
胡佛長官 我是特工布羅德貝克
Director Hoover, it's Special Agent Broadbeck.
我在皇家酒店現場
I'm here on site at the El Royale.
長官 我們遇到麻煩了
Sir, we have a problem.
五號房
大家早上好啊 讓我們來走一遍 來
Good morning, everyone. Let's have a listen, shall we?
卡 卡
Cut. Cut.
停下
Cut it.
好了 來 咱們休息一下
All right, let's take a break, everyone. Shall we?
達琳 我們單獨談幾句
And, Darlene, a word, please.
達琳
Darlene...
你知道 要跟我說上話 每小時要多少錢嗎
do you know how much my time is worth?
不太清楚 先生...
No, sir, um...
桑德先生
Mr. Sunday.
但哥倫比亞唱片公司知道
Well, Columbia Records does.
哥倫比亞唱片公司現在給我的報價是
Columbia Records currently values my time
每小時兩百美元
at $200 an hour.
如果是你的話
Are you currently in a position
你會拒絕
where you can afford to turn down...
對方出價二百 四百 或六百美金嗎
two, four, $600 when it's offered to you?
不 我不能
No, I'm not.
你浪費我價值六百美金的時間
$600 of my time...
還一直特立獨行地堅持 你說的那叫什麼來著
and still you wanted to stay, what was it?
"乾淨的嗓音"
"Fresh."
很顯然就等於前奏太平
Which apparently means flat on the intro
和聲又太尖銳
and sharp on harmonies.
我下次會做的更好 桑德先生 我保證
I'll get it right next time, Mr. Sunday. I promise.
是啊
Yeah.
你知道你的時間值多少錢嗎 達琳
Do you know how much your time is worth, Darlene?
一場十二美元
$12 a session.
不管一場時間有多久
No matter how long the session.
我感覺 你在我這的時間越長
Which, I suppose, means the longer I keep you,
你的價格就會越低
the less your time is worth.
對嗎
Right?
達琳
Darlene...
你現在有一個機會
I think that you have a choice here.
給我一年的時間
Give me one year of your time.
我可以讓你出名
I can make you a star.
你將會在
You'll be singing lead...
裡維艾拉擔任主唱
headlining the Riviera.
或者
Or...
你可以繼續浪費我的時間
you can continue to treat my time as disposable.
繼續唱價值十二美元的替補 直到沒有你的位置
Keep scrounging for $12 backup gigs until they dry up.
五年後 當你醒來的時候
Five years from now, you'll wake up...
你會發現自己在垃圾旅館混日子
find yourself shuffling between shit hotels...
乞求里諾發免費煎餅的那晚
begging for the opening slot on pancake night...
有你的位置
in Reno.
達琳
Darlene.
你明白的吧
Do we understand?
好
Good.
很好
All right then.
誰
Yes?
你好 達琳
Hello, Darlene.
是之前的弗林神父
It's Father Flynn from earlier.
我真的很抱歉 我剛才是不是太吵了
I'm so sorry. I was making too much noise, wasn't I?
不不不 沒事的
Oh, no. No, not at all.
我已經儘量保持安靜
I have to rehearse and I was trying
但是我得練歌
to keep it quiet, but...
我很抱歉 之後不會再打擾你了
I'm sorry, I won't bother you.
不 你沒有打擾到我
No, it was no bother.
正相反 您的歌唱十分悅耳
Quite the opposite, actually. It's lovely.
謝謝您
Thank you.
剛才唱的那首歌
That song that you were singing,
是你自己寫的嗎
did you write that?
不是的 作者是艾斯禮兄弟
Oh, no, it's by The Isley Brothers.
是你的兄弟寫的嗎
Your brothers wrote that?
不 這是一首很著名的曲子
No, um, it's a famous song.
以前在收音機裡放過
It's been on the radio.
這樣啊 我好久不聽收音機了
Oh. I don't know too much about the radio these days.
我過來只是想去大廳裡找點吃的
I was gonna go find some food in the lounge...
然後就想到 你可能也願意和我一起去
and I thought I'd see if you'd like to join?
這裡恐怕只剩下你會願意了
With this place, there's probably strength in numbers.
不了 謝謝你
No, that's all right.
你確定嗎 我請客哦
You sure? It's on me.
就當我聽到你優美的歌聲
Consider it payment.
給你的一點報酬
For letting me listen to you sing.
謝謝你的誇獎
That's a very nice thing to say.
何必要放個鈴在這呢
Why even have a bell?
恐怕這裡就剩下咱們兩個人了
I suspect we're on our own.
那我負責拿食物 你來看看有什麼能玩的?
I handle food. You handle entertainment?
成
Deal.
本台得到的消息稱
We're told both the husband and wife
此前報導的被刺數刀的夫婦
suffered multiple stab wounds...
在救護車到達之前均已身亡
and were dead when the deputies arrived.
伯納德·韋伯先生曾是馬里布社區中的明星級人物
Bernard Webber was well known in the Malibu community...
生前熱衷於慈善事業...
and was very active in local philanthropic endeavors...
十分關注無家可歸的兒童們
mostly concerning homeless children.
你真的不知道艾斯禮兄弟嗎
You really never heard of The Isley Brothers?
那我得給你補補課了
Then we have some work to do.
飲料
你這邊怎麼樣了
How are you making out over here?
顯然你的任務完成的
You're definitely better at your job
比我要好
than I am at mine.
你今晚想選哪個幸運食物
How lucky are you feeling tonight?
肯定不想選那個三明治
Definitely not eat-that-sandwich lucky.
吃派嗎
Pie?
可以的
Pie's good.
我們現在有了
We have a very good, uh...
不是 是指我聽到了你的歌聲後
Well, no. Now that I've heard you sing...
我們就能在瑪麗聖心堂建一個不錯的唱詩班了
we have a pretty good choir at the Heart of Mary.
其實我就是這麼出道的
That's actually how I got started.
教堂唱詩班
Church choir.
哇.
Ah.
在迪凱特唱的聖保羅福音
St. Paul's Evangelical in Decatur.
那邊是路德會 但我其實並不信教
Lutheran. But we don't have to get into that.
上帝原諒你了
You're forgiven.
而且我們唱的東西都很千篇一律
I'm sure we must've sung some of the same stuff.
你聽過"我主耶穌 讚美你"嗎
Do you know, um, Nearer, My God, to Thee?
聽過
Mmm.
還有"哈利路亞 歌頌上帝"呢
And Alleluia! Sing to Jesus?
知道
Mmm.
那"擁我入懷 把我高高舉起" 這首聽過嗎
What about Hold Me in Your Arms, Lift Me on High?
是嗎
Oh.
那是我第一次獨唱
That was my first solo.
這麼唱的
It goes...
聽過嗎
You got that?
說實話 我的記性
To be honest, my memory, um...
大不如前了
isn't quite what it was.
好吧
Okay.
我想再來杯棕櫚酒
I think I'm gonna have a toddy.
要來一杯嗎
Can I interest you?
不用了
No, I'm fine.
不喝嗎 你確定嗎
No? You sure?
沒什麼比寒冷的夜晚來杯熱威士卡更棒的了
Nothing like a warm whiskey on a cold night.
真的不用了 謝謝
I'm fine. Thank you.
你怎麼會來這兒的呢
So, what are you doing out here?
我現在住在貝爾斯菲爾德
Oh, I live in Bakersfield now,
但是明天要去里諾找份唱歌的工作
but I got a job singing in Reno tomorrow.
真不錯
Oh, that's exciting.
我可不會這麼來形容
That's not exactly the word I'd use
一份在基諾酒吧每天清晨6點就要開工的工作
to describe a 6:00 shift at the keno lounge.
但 總得打份工嘛
But, um, it's a job.
那你怎麼會來住這兒呢
Why are you staying here?
那不是份好工作
It's not a good job.
錢也給得不多
Don't pay nothing.
如果住在里諾的好酒店 我就入不敷出了
But if I stay in Reno proper, I'd be in the hole.
郊區更划算
Outskirts are cheaper.
也對
Ah.
為什麼弄得自己這麼辛苦
Why do it at all?
我也常常這麼問自己
You know, I ask myself the same question sometimes.
是嗎
Mmm.
為了能唱歌吧
Singing's singing.
你呢
How about you?
你怎麼跑到皇家酒店來了呢
How'd you end up at the El Royale?
我去奧克蘭看我哥哥
I was visiting my brother in Oakland...
我必須在天黑前找個地方停車
and, uh, I had to get off the road before dark.
我的眼睛晚上看不清路
Well, my eyes, they're no good at night.
麗思卡爾頓酒店已經訂滿了
And the Ritz-Carlton was booked...
所以我來這兒了
so here we are.
我猜教堂給的錢和基諾酒吧給的一樣少 是嗎
I'm guessing church pays about as much as a keno lounge?
沒錯
Mmm-hmm.
錢真的不多
About that, yeah.
你哥哥怎麼樣了
How about your brother?
你和他關係好嗎
You and him close?
以前很好
Used to be.
是的 以前不錯
Used to be, yeah.
是嗎
Hmm.
達琳
Darlene...
我能向你坦白一件事嗎
can I confess something to you?
剛才我說我的記憶大不如前
When I said that my memory isn't quite what it was...
我覺得可能要說得更明白點兒
I think I might have been understating things a bit.
從幾年前開始 我的記憶就
For the last couple of years, my recall...
出現了一些問題
well, I've been having problems with it.
這不僅僅是因為上了年紀的關係
And, uh, I don't think it's just my age.
我確定不是年齡的原因
I'm certain it's not just my age.
有時候我醒來
I wake up some days...
記不起我是誰
and I can't remember who I am.
今天早上你在停車場碰到我
The moments when I lose time.
那時候我忘記了時間
When you saw me earlier today in the parking lot...
其實 我完全都不知道
actually, I had completely forgotten
我在哪兒 我在幹什麼
where I was, what I was doing.
很奇怪的感覺 你知道吧 環顧四周
Strangest feeling. You know, you look around
你好像是另一個人
and you're someone else...
也不知道那一個人是誰
and you don't know who that is.
我能給你點建議嗎 神父
Can I say something, Father?
說吧
Please.
我覺得你應該去看醫生
I think you should see a doctor.
我去看過 醫生也同意我的看法
Yeah, I have, and he agrees with my assessment
說不止是年齡的關係
that it's not just age.
抱歉
I'm sorry.
我不是來博得你的"同行"
Oh, I'm not looking for pithy.
同情
Pithy.
我只是跟你說一下
I'm just letting you know
萬一我看起來有點崩潰
in case I've seemed scattered...
那並不是想要冒犯你 女士
I don't mean offense, ma'am.
沒事
No.
不會往心裡去的
None taken.
其實也挺好的
It might be for the best.
我生命中有一些部分回憶 並不值得留念
There are parts of my life that aren't worth remembering.
我也有那種回憶
I have those, too.
我要再來一杯
I could use another.
你確定不要跟我一起喝嗎
You sure I can't tempt you?
不 不用了
No, I'm fine.
真的嗎
Are you sure?
我的記憶力可能不太好
Now, I may have a spotty memory...
但我知道 讓一位年邁的神父獨自喝酒 可是很罪惡的
but I do recall it is a sin to let an old priest drink alone.
好吧 就一杯
All right. Just one.
真好
Grand.
也許我會有榮幸
Perhaps I can even tempt you...
再聽你唱一首歌
to grace me with a song again later?
神父 可不要得寸進尺
Don't push your luck, Father.
但是如果你明天正好在里諾
But if you happen to be in Reno tomorrow,
我6點上場
I go on at 6:00.
我想去
Oh, I'd like that.
我會去的
I'd like that.
但在那之前
But until then...
在我取回
In the course of
我們的裝備時
retrieving our equipment...
我發現了一個
I discovered another wiretap
連著幾個話筒的竊聽器
along with several other microphones.
你認得那個裝置嗎
Did you recognize the equipment?
我覺得那不是我們的 長官
I don't believe they were ours, sir.
此外 我發現
Additionally, I discovered
賓館的房間裝有雙向鏡
the hotel room had a two-way mirror.
我還發現其他房間
I also found several other hotel rooms
沿著觀景走廊 裝有相同裝置
with the same setup along an observation corridor...
還有攝像頭
as well as a camera.
你找到膠捲了嗎
Did you find film?
沒有 我一找到攝像頭就打電話通知您了
No, I called in as soon as I found the camera.
我們必須設想
We must assume
我們的行動已經處於危險之中了
our operation has been compromised.
任何人都不准離開那 特工布羅德貝克
No one is to leave there, Agent Broadbeck...
直到你
until you have any and all
拿到監控視頻資料
existing surveillance materials in your possession.
明白 長官
Understood, sir.
長官 我還有其他的事情要彙報
Sir, there is something else.
我在走廊上調查後發現
Upon investigating the observation corridor...
我推測這裡曾經發生過綁架
I came across what appeared to be a kidnapping in process.
一個年輕的女士 白人
A young woman, Caucasian,
在這裡綁架了另一個年輕的女士
appeared to be holding another young woman hostage.
也是白人
Also Caucasian.
現在最重要的是拿到監控視頻資料
The priority is the surveillance materials,
布羅德貝克特工
Agent Broadbeck.
其他的事情 不用我們多費心
Peripheral matters are not our concern.
長官
Sir...
我不想再重複我說的話
I am not in the habit of repeating myself,
布羅德貝克特工
Agent Broadbeck...
但我會一直重複 直到確保你沒有疑問
but I will do so here to ensure there is no confusion.
七號房
嗨
Hiya!
Hi.
我喜歡你的靴子
I like your boots.
這是我爸爸的
They're my daddy's.
現在看上去不像是你爸爸的鞋了
Well, they don't look like your daddy's no more.
這是你傷心的原因嗎
Is that why you're so sad?
我們這裡沒有很多女孩穿靴子的
We don't get a lot of girls down here in boots.
你是從車站那邊來的 對嗎
You must have come straight from the station, huh?
沒事 小靴子 你什麼都不用對我說
It's all right, Boots. You don't got to say nothin'.
3次以內 我就能猜到你從哪來的
I'll figure it out in three guesses. Watch.
田納西州
Tennessee?
不可能 那太簡單了
Nah, that's too easy.
我確定你不是來自德克薩斯
You ain't no Texas girl. I know that much for sure.
西維吉尼亞
West Virginia?
不 也不可能
Nah, of course not.
不要侮辱她 比利·李
Don't insult the girl, Billy Lee.
我只是和你鬧著玩
Hey, I'm just messing with you.
當我看到沙灘上的靴子腳印時
I knew it the second I saw
我就知道你是哪裡人了
these boot prints on the beach.
你來自阿拉巴馬州
You're an Alabama girl.
是吧
See?
早就告訴你 我能猜到的
Told you I could do it in three.
現在 你得來和我一起游泳
Now, you gotta come swimming with me.
我剛才可沒答應你這個
That wasn't the deal.
當然要答應了
Sure it was.
我們才開始玩的時候 你就知道我什麼意思了
You knew the game the second we started playing.
快來 小靴子 你沒有道理再哭了
Come on, Boots. You got no reason to cry no more.
你現在可是在加利福尼亞呢
You're in California now.
羅斯
Rose?
羅西
Rosie.
羅斯 沒事
Rose, hey. It's okay.
沒事
It's okay.
你現在很安全 你跟我在一起呢
You're safe. You're with me.
沒事 沒事
It's okay. It's okay.
你這樣我沒法給你解開
Rosie, I can't untie you.
停下
Stop it.
我知道你現在對我很生氣
I expect you're all kinds of mad at me,
從某種程度上來說 你有權利生我的氣
and to some extent you're right to be...
但是我們會一起挺過去的
but we're gonna wait this out.
我要先讓你想明白
I'm gonna get you clear...
然後我們再把事情說清楚
and then we can have it out.
我們要離他越遠越好
We have to get as far away from him as possible.
他十惡不赦
He's all kinds of bad.
無論你之前做過什麼 現在都無所謂了羅斯
It doesn't matter what you did, Rose.
我馬上還你清白
I'm gonna get you clear...
然後我們重新來過
and then we'll just start over.
女士
Ma'am?
你好 很抱歉打擾您
Hello. I'm sorry to disturb you.
你想幹什麼
What do you want?
女士 是這樣的 我是拉勒米·蘇利文
Oh. Ma'am, yeah. It's Laramie Sullivan.
我們先前在酒店大堂見過面
We met in the hotel lobby there earlier?
介意開下門嗎
Would you mind opening the door?
不 我不會開的
No, I ain't gonna do that.
我完全
I certainly
理解
understand that, yes.
小心點總是好的
It's good to be cautious.
你要是願意的話 我們就隔著門談吧
We can talk through the door, if you like.
你想幹什麼
What do you want?
是這樣的 女士 外面的風暴
Oh, well, ma'am, the storm's just wreckin'
正在對酒店百般摧殘
all kinds of hell on the hotel.
住客們正在抱怨停電 還有其他什麼的
People are having complaints about losing power and such...
所以前臺那小子讓我來轉轉
and so the boy up front had asked me to come around...
看看女士們是否安然無恙
check on some of the women and make sure they're safe.
我沒事
I'm fine.
好吧 很好 那就好
Well, that's good to hear. That's good to hear.
聽我說 如果你不介意的話...
Uh, listen, if you wouldn't mind...
滾
Fuck off.
很抱歉 讓您受驚了 女士
I'm very sorry to have spooked you, ma'am.
願您度過一個安然無恙的夜晚
You have a safe night.
嘿 嘿 嘿 看著我
Hey, hey, hey. Look at me!
沒事了 沒事的
It's gonna be okay. It's okay.
冷靜了嗎 沒事了
Okay? It's okay.
你現在安全了
You're safe now.
我來給你鬆綁
Let's get you untied.
別碰
Don't touch it.
你讓它流血了
You let it bleed.
下次學聰明點
Next time you wanna get smart,
看看那些血紅的一片 以後要三思而後行
look down at all that red and think twice.
羅西哪去了
Where's Rosie?
羅西 羅西
Rosie, Rosie?
你不要出來 好不好
Don't you come out, okay?
無論你聽到什麼 只管待在這裡
No matter what you hear, you stay put.
羅西去哪了
Where's Rosie?
不管聽到什麼 都別發出聲音
No matter what you hear, don't make a sound.
好了 聽我說
Okay, listen to me.
你再也不必感到害怕了
You don't have to be afraid anymore.
好的
Okay, good.
羅西
Rosie.
讓開
Get out of the way.
聽著
Listen.
弗林神父
Father Flynn.
神父
Father?
弗林神父
Father Flynn.
不要動 神父
Hey. Don't try to move, Father.
我不是你爸爸
I'm not your father.
慢慢來 小心點來
Take it easy. Take it real easy.
怎麼會發生這種事呢
What the heck happened?
這是什麼歌
Oh, what's this song?
神父 你知道你在哪嗎
Father, do you know where you are?
發生了什麼
What happened?
我還想問你呢
That's what I'm asking you.
我找到你的時候 你就像這樣躺在地上
I just found you like this. On the floor.
你頭上紮進了玻璃
You got glass in your head.
這是哪裡
Where...?
只有我一個人嗎
Was I alone?
對啊 怎麼了 你剛和誰在一起嗎
Yeah. Why? Was you with somebody?
不
No.
孩子 你叫什麼來著
Kid, what's your name again?
熱門電影字幕歡迎關注微博 @遠鑒字幕組v
若是想施展您的翻譯才華 讓自己的名字出現在字幕開頭
遠鑒字幕組歡迎您加入 遠鑒字幕組招新群 483552098
彎彎字幕組招新群 562846983
招募各語種翻譯 誠邀您的加入
米爾斯
Miles.
米爾斯 我需要喝一杯
Miles. I need a drink.
給我倒杯酒
Fix me a drink.
我可不覺得那是個好主意
Oh, I'm not so sure that's a good idea.
觀眾您好
如果給您分發的資源的人未明確指出是遠鑒字幕組作品
或是裁剪\去除掉了片頭的字幕組製作人資訊
說明您可能獲取的是二手資源
就一杯酒 用來醒腦提神
Just one drink to clear my head.
獲取一手資源 拒絕二手資源 從您做起
更多精彩內容 敬請關注微博 @遠鑒字幕組v
我會去拿 但你看看這一切
I'd get it myself, but look what happens.
米爾斯 我摔倒了
Miles, I fell down.
我老了
I'm old.
常會發生這種事 拿威士卡來
Shit happens. Get the whiskey.
神父
Father...
我希望
I was hopin'...
我希望得到你的幫助
I was hopin' I could ask for your help.
我離開
I've been gone...
離開教堂已經有一段時間了
gone from the church for a while now.
但我這一生都是虔誠的
But I was devout my whole life.
我受洗禮 受堅信禮
Baptized, confirmed...
離開印第安那州前 我從未錯過禮拜日
never missed a Sunday till I left Indiana.
我生在印第安那州
I was born in Indiana.
真的嗎 你沒開玩笑嗎
Really? No kiddin'?
在什麼地方
Whereabouts?
好吧
Okay.
神父 我希望 聽著
Father, I was hopin', see...
我有些事情想要告解
I got things I need to confess.
現在不是時候 孩子
Not now, kid.
好吧 神父
Okay, Father. Right.
當然
Of course.
只是
It's just...
我很後悔 神父
I'm penitent, Father.
我真的很後悔
I promise I'm penitent.
我良心上過不去
And I'm afraid for my soul.
我做了可怕的事情
I've done horrible things.
那又怎麼樣 每個人都做過
So? So has everybody.
你會沒事的
You'll be fine.
你有這地方的萬能鑰匙嗎
You have a master key to this place?
你把自己鎖在房間外面了嗎
Did you lock yourself out of your room?
我之前說過的 孩子 老了
Like I said, kid, I'm old.
我老了
I'm old.
應該就在這裡的呀
Should be right here.
神父
Father...
鑰匙呢
Where's the key?
米爾斯
Miles.
我告訴過你
I told you...
這兒不是個好地方 神父
this wasn't a good place, Father.
你監視我?
You watched me?
你都看見了什麼
What did you see?
我什麼都沒看見 我沒有 我沒有
I didn't see nothing! I didn't, I didn't.
我只監視他們要求我監視的人
I only watch who they tell me to watch.
"他們"是誰
Who's "they"?
上頭的人
Management.
只要接到電話
I get a call...
"某某人在辦理入住手續了 把攝像頭準備好"
"So-and-so is checking in, set up the camera."
但自從選舉以來 沒發生過什麼大事
Hasn't happened much since the election.
通常他們想要的只是 你懂的 拍人們滾床單的畫面
Mostly they just want, you know, people screwin'.
你怎麼處理這些膠捲
What do you do with the film?
在後面這些小屋子裡 把它們沖洗出來
Develop it in one of the back cabins,
然後寄給上頭
mail it to management.
地址在賓夕法尼亞州
P.O. box in Pennsylvania.
你有保留過這些膠捲嗎
Do you ever keep any of the film?
你保留過嗎
Do you ever keep any of it?
說話啊
Miles?
去年 有場隆重的慶祝活動
Last year. The big celebration.
有個男人和我們在一塊
A man stayed with us.
他可是個大人物 你或許認識他
He was a big deal, you would know him.
上頭想要他的把柄 他們真的想扳倒他
Management wanted him. They really wanted him.
但是他對我很好
But he was kind to me.
沒有人曾這樣對過我
Nobody's ever kind to me...
所以我告訴上頭 他的房間裡沒有女人
so I told them there wasn't no woman in his room.
那麼你扣下了膠捲
So you kept it, the film?
神父 這都算不上我想告解的內容
Father, this ain't even what I was trying to confess.
我幹過比這更糟糕的事
I've done so much worse than this.
誰在那兒
Who is that?
老天啊
Oh, Jesus!
沒事了
It's okay.
你現在很安全
You're safe.
有我在呢
You're with me.
我們要幫幫她
We gotta help her.
我們要幫她 神父
We gotta help her, Father.
我們必須做點什麼 幫幫她吧
We gotta do something. We gotta help her.
米爾斯 聽我說 米爾斯
Miles, listen to me. Miles!
聽著
Listen to me.
上帝要你告訴我 膠捲在哪
The Lord wants you to tell me where the film is.
他十惡不赦
He's all kinds of bad.
弗林神父
Father Flynn.
女士 在嗎
Ma'am? Hello?
很抱歉打擾您
I'm so sorry to bother you.
你想幹什麼
What do you want?
女士 我是拉勒米·蘇利文
Ma'am, it's Laramie Sullivan.
弗林神父
Father Flynn!
神父 快來
Father Flynn, get down here!
那個吸塵器男剛剛撞開了門
That vacuum man just busted down the door...
他打了另一個女孩 手裡還拿著槍
and he beat up that other girl, and he's got a gun!
離窗戶遠點 孩子
Get away from the window! Kid!
救救我
Help me.
救命
Help.
這他媽是怎麼回事
What the fuck?
老天啊 該死
Jesus fucking Christ!
神父 別得寸進尺了
Don't push your luck, Father.
但如果你明天恰好也在里諾
But if you happen to be in Reno tomorrow,
我六點上臺
I go on at 6:00.
我想去的
Oh, I'd like that.
但在那之前...
But until then...
快
Come on.
快啊 快點啊
Come on! Come on!
主啊...
Lord...
我需要您的指引
I need your guidance.
我正身處黑暗 我需要您的聖光
I'm in darkness, and I need your light.
羅斯 讓開
Rose, get out of the way.
上帝啊
Jesus fucking Christ!
羅西
Rosie...
你就待在這兒
you stay here.
請別殺...
Please don't kill...
快
Come on.
把你的手放在我他媽能看見的地方
Keep your fucking hands where I can see them.
你在幹什麼
What are you doing?
是我
Hi, it's me.
我不知道
I don't know.
我和艾姆在一起
I'm with Em.
她剛把我綁起來了 好像還殺了那個員警
She had me all tied up. Think she shot a cop.
我們在酒店裡
We're in a hotel.
我不知道
I don't know.
你會嗎
You will?
好的
Okay.
我看看
Let me look.
這個酒店叫"皇家酒店"
It says "El Royale."
羅西
Rosie!
羅西 過來
Rosie, get in here.
我得掛了
I gotta go.
好 再見
Okay. See you again soon.
羅西
Rosie!
快啊 快啊
Come on! Come on!
不不不
No, no, no!
主啊...
Lord...
我只是想談談
I just wanna talk.
搖下車窗
Roll down the window.
我只是想談談 我能進來嗎
I just wanna talk. Can I get in?
相信我
I will shoot you in the face.
我會一槍崩了你
Believe me.
我信你
I believe you.
但我們現在遇到點麻煩了
Well, we're in a bit of a pickle here.
很抱歉 我剛在大廳裡試圖給你下藥
I'm sorry that I tried to drug you back there in the lobby.
我不是想騙你什麼的
I wasn't trying to diddle you or nothing like that...
我只是想進你的房間
I just needed to break into your room.
我沒想著要傷害你
And I didn't wanna hurt you.
我是說 我沒必要傷害你
Any more than need be, I mean.
這麼跟你說吧 你不用因為打了我
No hard feelings about bashing me in the head
而感到愧疚
is what I'm saying.
我敢肯定那些女孩殺了個員警還是什麼的
I'm pretty sure those girls killed a cop of some sort.
確實
They did.
你看見了
You saw it?
是的
Yeah.
那是他的槍
That his gun?
是的
Mmm-hmm.
這對我們來說 可不是好消息
This is not so good for us.
我其實不是什麼神父
I'm not really a priest.
沒什麼大不了
Yeah, no shit.
-他們死了嗎  -沒有 還活著
- Are they dead? - Nah, they'll live.
你在哪兒學的開車呀
Where'd you learn to drive?
是他們突然轉向
They swerved.
是他們轉了 但你當時正準備掃過去攔他們
Yeah, they tend to do that when you're box sweepin' 'em.
"跟著他的擋泥板" 你說的 "我要讓他們害怕"
"Stay on his fender," you said. "I want him scared."
是害怕 不是讓他們昏迷
"Scared," not comatose.
來了
Oh, here we go.
他們死了嗎
Are they dead?
好吧
Okay.
你到底怎麼開車的
Where'd you learn to drive?
我們已經談過這個了
We've been over this!
閉嘴 拿了錢就走
Shut the fuck up! Get the money!
他們沒死
They ain't dead.
感謝上帝
Praise the Lord.
可不能把這車留在這兒
Well, can't leave this here.
是的
Yeah.
可以啟動嗎
Will it run?
可以的 走吧
Let's go with yes.
你覺得這個新人是故意的還是傻
Think the new guy is bent or just stupid?
我覺得他是傻 但是我也沒法確定
Oh, I'm going with stupid, but I can be persuaded.
我們這是在幹什麼呢 道克
What are we doing, Dock?
下車
Get out of the car.
下車 菲力克斯
Get out of the car, Felix.
來 來
Here, here.
把孩子帶走
Take the kid...
把雪佛蘭丟在克林市 分頭行動
ditch the Chevy at Rocklin. Split up.
我把他們領到南邊
I'll lead 'em south,
等沒人追我了 我就把這些都燒了
I'll burn this once I'm in the clear.
我們在皇家酒店碰面 好嗎
We all meet at the El Royale, huh?
菲力克斯
Felix.
你和這些混蛋走得很近 是嗎
You play it close with these assholes. Huh?
你確定這樣做嗎 道克
You sure about this, Dock?
我們能搞定的 菲力克斯 小菜一碟
Oh, we got this, Felix, piece of cake.
一切盡在掌控之中
I got it under control.
全體起立
All rise.
唐納德·奧凱利
Donald O'Kelly...
你被指控與人合謀
on the charges of grand larceny
犯下巨額竊盜案
and conspiracy to commit larceny...
我判你 在聯邦監獄待15年
I sentence you to 15 years in the federal penitentiary.
什麼 哪兒
What? Where?
-道克  -我在哪兒
- Dock.  - Where am I?
嘿 嘿 道克
Hey, hey, Dock.
沒事的
It's okay.
什麼 我到底在哪
What? Where am I?
一個他媽你都待了10年的地方了
Same place you've been the last ten fucking years.
你會好起來的 兄弟
You're gonna be okay, man.
上帝啊 道克
Jesus, Dock.
我們得去看看醫生
We gotta do something about this.
你怎麼看
What do you think?
我覺得你現在開始
I think you should stop fighting
最好別和那個黑鬼打架了
with the negroes, for starters.
墨西哥 墨西哥人
Mesican... Mesican...
墨西哥人
Mexicans.
對 這次是和他們
Yeah, them this time.
我什麼也沒做
And I didn't do nothing.
那你真的做了什麼的時候 得成什麼樣啊
Hate to see what happens when you do something.
好吧
Oh, well.
再告訴我一遍 樓下那個男孩是不是再也不能走路了
Tell me that boy down the hall may not walk again.
是他撲過來的
He jumped me.
行吧 行吧
Mmm-hmm. Yeah, sure.
這事和打架無關
It's not about the fighting.
對
No.
的確和打架無關
It's not about the fightin'.
給我說說你的家族吧
Tell me about your family.
有什麼病史嗎 有過癡呆 或者阿茲海默嗎
Any history? Dementia? Alzheimer's?
我母親
My mother.
她的父親有過
Her father.
我還有多長時間
How long I got?
你想什麼時候申請保釋
When you up for parole?
六個月後
Six months.
你能撐到那個時候的
You should make it till then.
菲力克斯 我的兄弟 和我...
Felix, my brother, and I...
我們在斯托克頓城外搶了一輛武裝的車
we robbed an armored car, outside of Stockton.
事情進展得不怎麼好
The job went bad.
我覺得我們肯定被自已人出賣了
I think we got burned by our crew.
接頭的時候菲力克斯被殺了
Felix was killed at the meetup,
就是在這裡 在皇家酒店
which was here, at the El Royale.
我們有個計畫B 以防事情敗露
We had a plan in case things went south.
把錢埋在房間的地板下麵
Bury the money in the floor of the room.
我記不清我們說的是哪間房間了
I couldn't remember what room we said.
不是四號房的話 就是五號房
It was either four or five.
之前我給你說的 都是事實
It's true what I told you back there.
我的腦子有時候會很混亂
My mind, it isn't what it was.
我選錯房間了
I guessed wrong.
所以 我想你房間的地板下面
So, I think there's a bunch of money
應該埋了很多很多的錢 達琳
buried in your room, Darlene...
我需要你的幫忙 幫我找到它
and I need your help to get it.
你覺得 我會相信你說的這些話嗎
You expect me to believe all that?
但這些都是事實啊
Well, it's the truth.
確實是事實 所以我們才會在這
It's the truth, so there is that.
不 好吧 我懂了
But, no, I get it.
你是怎麼從一開始
How did you know I wasn't
就知道我在說謊呢
on the up and up in the first place?
如果你的一生都非常不幸
You spend your life getting shook,
你就能輕易識破一個說謊的人
you learn how to spot a shaker.
這是哪首歌的歌詞嗎
Is that from a song?
不是
No.
如果你想錯了
If you'd have been wrong...
你就毫無理由地打了一個神父
you'd have bashed a priest in the face for no reason.
我會找個理由原諒我自已的
I would've found a way to forgive myself.
是啊 如果我處在跟你一樣的位置
Yeah, I guess I'd have done the same thing
我也會做同樣的事
in your situation.
那現在呢
And now?
如果你是我的話 你會怎麼做
What would you do if you were me?
這個嘛... 我的第一個念頭會是
Well, my first impulse would be
殺了我面前的那個老男人
to shoot the old man in the face...
把錢洗劫一空
and clear out of Dodge.
你說得太對了
You're dead right.
但是 我會想得很遠一點
Oh, but I would think that through.
你看 車已經壞了
You know, the cars aren't working.
這暴風雨也沒有停的跡象
The storm's not lettin' up.
有人遲早會過來找
People are gonna come looking
那個死了的員警
for that dead cop soon enough...
而且當他們找到我的時候 我也不想自己是一個
and I don't want to be the black woman
在大黑天裡的森林中拿著槍的黑女人
in the woods at night with a gun when they do.
所以 我得重新想一些別的辦法
So then, I'd start thinking about my other options.
我認為我可以回去
I suppose I could go back in there...
找那些孩子碰碰運氣
take my chances with those kids.
我可從來沒這麼想過
I promise you I'm not thinking that.
於是我做了第三個決定
Which leads me to option three.
也許我該聽那個老男人的 也許他說的是實話
Maybe I hear the old man out, maybe he's telling the truth.
也許真的有錢藏在我房間裡
Maybe there really is money buried in my room.
也許那個老傢伙
Maybe the old man...
他沒多少時間好活了
he doesn't have a lot of time left.
所以或許他拿走一半地板下面的錢就滿足了
He's fine with 50% of whatever we find in that floor.
如果我猜錯了 到時候還是能一槍崩了他
If I'm wrong, I can still shoot him later, huh?
但如果我猜對了
But if I'm right...
我今晚可能就能活下來了
I might just survive tonight.
如果我猜對了
If I'm right...
我還可以帶著一大筆錢走出去
I can walk out of here with enough money
徹底改變我的生活
to change my life forever.
你說的錢 到底有多少
How much money are we talking exactly?
所以
So...
這是什麼 色情主題酒店嗎
What is this? Some kind of pervert hotel?
跟你說話呢
Hey.
不是
No.
是的
Yes...
我不知道
I don't know.
你就一槍崩了我吧
You just shot me in the face.
好吧 現在我們把話說明白點
Well, now, let's be clear.
我剛剛崩了一個找死的人
I shot another man who had it comin'...
而你剛好偷偷摸摸到那裡去了
and you just happened to be back there being creepy...
因為你多管閒事 所以你現在臉上全是彈孔
and you caught a face full of buckshot for your trouble.
等一下 別動
Wait, hold still a sec.
你頭上有碎玻璃
You got glass in your head.
我現在看上去怎麼樣
How does it look?
老實說 我不太記得
To be honest, I don't remember
在這之前 你長什麼樣的了
what you looked like before this.
但我認為你應該坦然面對
But I think you should make peace
你這張臉已經毀了的現實
with the fact that things have changed.
你要殺了我嗎
Are you gonna kill me?
你看到了不該看到的 我能不殺你嗎
How can I not after what you've seen?
我看到過更糟的
I seen worse.
而且我什麼也沒說
And I ain't said a thing.
你還能看到比
You've seen worse than a man
一個男人被槍崩成兩半 更慘的嗎
getting sawn in half with a shotgun?
我見過各種各樣的慘劇
I seen all sorts of bad.
我看到過
I seen, um...
一個議員毫無人性地毆打一個妓女
a senator beat up a whore so bad...
她的牙齒都被打掉了
she had to shove her own stockings
逼她把自己的長襪塞進嘴裡
back where her teeth used to be...
來堵住不停流出來的血
just to keep from bleeding out through the mouth.
我還看到過
I saw...
一個癮君子 用他的糞便在牆上塗寫下"抱歉"二字
a junkie paint "Sorry" on the wall in his own filth.
好像這樣能讓我更容易
Like that'd make it easier
清理他冰冷屍體上的糞便一樣
when I cleaned all that shit off his cold body.
我還曾有次看到一個人和狼睡在一起
I saw a man lay with a wolf once.
那傢伙拉來了一頭純灰的野狼
Guy drags a full-grown feral wolf
用一個他房間裡項圈
on a choke chain into his room...
把它系在床頭
ties it up to the bed...
然後他脫掉了所有的衣服
and takes off all his clothes...
爬上床 到狼的邊上 手裡抓著那玩意兒...
climbs into bed beside it, and holds the thing.
一整晚
All night.
你不能說那是性...
It wasn't sexual...
你也不能說那不是性...
but it wasn't not sexual, either.
那個男人一邊幹一邊喊 “幫幫我...”
Guy just laid there crying, sayin', "Help me..."
野狼就那麼被他壓著
while he held that wolf.
一整晚
All night.
我從來沒有和任何人說過這些
I never told nobody about none of that.
天呐...
Oh...
其實我也不確定你是不是應該告訴我這些
I ain't so sure you should've told me that.
其實...
Uh...
你並不需要殺我
You don't have to kill me.
關於你 我能說什麼呢
What could I even say about you, anyway?
"幾個女的殺了幾個男的 因為那幾個男的想殺她們"
"Some girls shot some guy who was gonna shoot them"?
我都不知道你們的名字
I don't even know your names.
我叫羅斯
I'm Rose.
別說了...
Don't say...
羅斯·莎莫斯普林
Rose Summerspring.
這是我姐姐艾米莉
That's my sister, Emily.
你叫什麼名字
What's your name?
米爾斯
Miles.
米爾斯·米勒
Miles Miller.
很高興認識你 米爾斯
Well, it's nice to meet you, Miles.
其他的人都在哪兒
Where are the others?
你是叫羅斯 對嗎
Rose? That's your name, right?
求你了 羅斯 別殺我
Please, Rose. Please don't kill me.
這不是我能決定的
It ain't entirely up to me.
你可以和她談
You can talk to her.
她是你姐姐 她會聽你的
She's your sister, she'll listen to you.
這也不是她能決定的
It ain't up to her either.
誰能決定
Well, who's it up to?
神父在哪兒
Where's the priest?
米爾斯
Miles...
我不知道
I don't know.
不過 你總知道些什麼吧
But you do know something, don't you?
這是你的嗎
Is this yours?
你想要嗎
Do you want it?
神父在哪兒
Where's the priest?
我真的不知道
I don't know.
我發誓
I promise.
我也想找到他
I wanna find him too.
求你了
Please.
你讓我做什麼都可以
I'll do whatever you want.
當你找到他的時候 讓我和他說句話
Just let me talk to the priest when you find him.
在你殺我之前 也讓我和他說句話
Just let me talk to him before you kill me.
我已經暗示他了
I've been trying to tell him
我們並不一定要殺了他
that we might not have to kill him.
但我們說了不算
But it's not up to us.
誰說了算呢 羅斯
Who's it up to, Rose?
羅斯 你做了什麼
Rose, what did you do?
你好啊
Howdy.
比利·李
你想和我們一起待多久
So how long you lookin' to stay with us?
我姐待多久 我就待多久咯
However long my sister stays, I suppose.
不 僅僅因為一點血緣關係
No, you don't get to be a part of the family
並不代表你就是家庭中的一員
just 'cause you're kin.
你為什麼會想待在這兒
Why do you wanna be here?
羅西說你對她挺好的
Rosie says you treat her pretty nice.
很感謝你
I appreciate that.
上帝對你來說意味著什麼
What does God mean to you?
上帝對你們所有人來說意味著什麼
What does God mean to all of you?
他一直高高在上嗎
Is He some being in the sky?
你會在夜晚對他禱告嗎
Do you pray to Him at night?
你有沒有讓他庇佑你
Do you ask Him to watch over you?
他現在與我們同在嗎
Is He here with us now?
或者說這裡 根本就沒有上帝
Or maybe there is no God, huh?
或許這一切都是謊言
Maybe it's all lies.
我沒說我自己 把一切都搞清楚了
Listen, I ain't saying I got it all figured out.
我沒有 但是我知道遊戲規則
I'm not. But I do see the game.
他們定義了對與錯 然後讓你們來選擇
They define right and wrong, and then they make you choose.
這就是一切的開始 一個簡單的選擇
And that's how it all starts, with a simple choice...
你選擇站在哪邊
which side are you on?
上邊 下邊 好的 壞的 對的 錯的
Up, down? Good, evil? Right, wrong?
有神或無神 很簡單 只是選擇
God or no God? It's simple, just pick.
小靴子 快選 你是好人還是壞人
Boots. Quick. Choose. Are you good or are you bad?
都不是
I'm neither.
她在撒謊 因為她知道
Now, she's cheating 'cause she knows
我想要什麼樣的答案
what answer I'm looking for.
小靴子 我在這群人面前演講呢
Boots, I'm giving a whole speech here
別把它搞砸了
in front of people. Don't mess it up for me.
他們都讓你選
They'll get you to pick.
看著
Watch.
我現在要這樣做
I'll do it right now.
我現在要讓我的明星學生這樣做
I'll do it right now with my star pupil.
小靴子 上來
Boots, why don't you come up here
幫我個忙
and help me out for a sec?
還有…
And, what about...
米莉 你也上來
Millie, why don't you come join us, too.
快來
Come on.
今晚我們會有一場拳鬥
We're gonna have ourselves a tussle tonight.
離上次的拳鬥有一段時間了
It's been a while since we've had a tussle, right?
等等 羅西不想上場
Oh, but wait a second. Rosie don't wanna tussle.
她很聰明 知道不應該參加這場比賽
She's smart enough to know not to play the game, right?
看我的
But this is how I get her.
我會給她她想要的
I dangle something she really wants.
今晚你們倆進行這場獨一無二的拳鬥
You two are gonna have a proper tussle tonight...
勝利者
and the winner...
勝利者可以跟我一起睡
Well, the winner gets to sleep with me
今晚 睡在豪宅裡 怎麼樣
in the big house tonight. How'd that be?
看到沒
See?
就像他們說的 讓參與者和這遊戲利益相關
Now we got skin in the game, as they say.
所以小靴子你怎麼看 想上場嗎
So what do you think, Boots? You wanna play?
是的
Yes.
那麼 選一邊站隊吧
So, pick a side.
你想在對的一邊還是錯的一邊
Do you wanna be Right or do you wanna be Wrong?
對的一邊
I wanna be Right.
她想在對的一邊
She wants to be Right.
那麼 米莉 我想你在錯的一邊
Well, Millie, I guess that makes you Wrong.
讓我們來創造歷史吧
Let's have ourselves an allegory.
好的 開始
All right. Have at it.
艾米莉別激動
Whoa. Easy, Emily.
她是個大孩子了 能夠照顧好自己
She's a big girl. She can take care of herself.
現在最重要的是
Now, here's the important part.
她們在打架 我該幹些什麼呢
While they're fighting, what am I doing, huh?
我肯定不會參與其中啊 那我幹嘛
'Cause I sure as hell ain't fighting. What am I doing?
我就在旁邊看著他們
I'm watching them.
我就置身事外 然後我來這邊
I'm getting off on it. Then I'm coming over here...
拿走屬於他們的東西
and I'm takin' what's theirs.
但是他們完全不會知道
And they didn't even notice...
因為他們在忙著打我的比賽
'cause they're too busy playing my game.
好了好了
All right, all right.
羅西 羅西
Rosie, Rosie.
行了 過來 好了好了
Come on. Hey, okay, okay.
好了好了 比賽結束 行嗎
All right, all right. Tussle's over, okay?
夠了 比賽結束
Okay, tussle's over.
羅西 羅西
Rosie, Rosie.
比賽結束了
Hey, tussle's over.
你們要學會愛對方
Love each other.
行了行了
All right, all right.
你做得挺好 你們兩個都不錯 行了
You did good. Both did good. Okay.
所以 我們學到了什麼
So, what have we learned, huh?
可能我們需要 再也不玩他們的那些比賽了
Maybe we won't play their games no more.
可能我們需要 再也不聽信他們的謊言
Maybe we won't listen to their lies.
可能這世上唯一的真理 就在這裡
Maybe the only truth in this world is right here.
這裡
And here.
And here...
這裡 這裡
and here, and here...
這裡 我們之間
and here. Just us.
也許今晚
And maybe for tonight...
我們可以做我們自己的神
we get to be our own Gods.
弗林神父
Father Flynn.
保佑我 神父 因我的罪孽深重
Bless me, Father, for I have sinned.
求你了 神父
Please, Father...
孩子 你要是不閉嘴 我就把你的嘴縫上
Kid, if you don't shut up, I'm gonna tie your mouth shut.
神父 求你了 原諒我所犯的罪
Father, please, forgive me for the sins of my life.
求你了 神父
Please, Father...
不不不
No, no, no.
所以 我猜 你是弗林神父
So, I'm guessing you're Father Flynn.
所以那個死人是拉勒米·西摩·蘇利文
Which makes the dead guy Laramie Seymour Sullivan.
然後 女士你肯定就是達琳·斯維特對吧
And you, miss, must be Darlene Sweet. Hmm?
或許 你可能是那個”操你媽”
Well, I suppose you could be Fuck You...
但我的直覺告訴我 我的艾米莉在這裡
but, uh, something tells me that's my Emily here.
還有其他人在這個旅館裡嗎
Any other people in the hotel?
還有嗎
Hmm?
韋德 安娜貝拉
Wade, Annabell...
站在他們四個後面
stand behind these four,
如果他們想要離開座位
and if they try to get out of those seats...
你們可以直接爆了他們
you just shoot 'em in the back of the head.
弗裡克 羅曼 來這邊
Flicker, Roman, come here.
去七號房 找到那個死人
Go to room seven, get the dead guy...
然後把他的屍體和他的東西
and put all of his stuff
都放進車的後備箱裡
and the body in the trunk of the car.
再一間一間得找找 有沒有其他人
Then go room to room, see if you can find anybody else.
如果有的話把他們帶過來
If you can, you bring 'em here.
那他們呢
What about them?
我還有一些問題
Well, first I got some questions
要他們回答
that need answering.
記得在車上留些地方
But leave some room in the trunk.
你好啊艾姆
Hiya, Em.
比利·李
Billy Lee.
你呀
You know, uh...
你走的時候都沒打聲招呼
you left without saying goodbye.
你覺得我不會生氣嗎
What'd you think, I wouldn't take offense? Hmm?
不 我猜到了你會生氣
Naw, I figured you would.
但我以為那時候 我已經準備好了
But I'd be ready when you did.
你看著不像是準備好了
You don't look ready.
今晚時機不對 被你抓住了
You caught me on a bad night.
很不巧 對吧
Ain't that the luck, huh?
你和他們說沒說 她都幹了些什麼
Did you tell 'em what she did? Hmm?
你說沒說
Did you tell them what she did?
我幹什麼了
What'd I do?
哦 那個啊
Oh, right.
不好意思啦
Sorry about all that.
她說不好意思了
She's sorry.
沒關係 小靴子 等我們回到加州之後
It's all right, Boots. We'll deal with that
我們會把事情都處理好的
when we get back to California.
現在 要先把內華達這兒的問題解決了
We got us a Nevada problem now.
所以 米爾斯
So, uh, Miles...
這裡是什麼情況 你們是什麼變態酒店嗎
What is this? Some sort of pervert hotel?
那孩子沒法回答你
Kid can't answer you.
你把他的嘴堵上了
You tied his mouth shut.
那我不如問問你吧
Well, why don't I ask you then? Huh?
讓我來問問這個
Why don't I ask the priest who was walking
拎著滿滿一包錢走出了酒店的神父吧
out of the hotel with a bag full of money?
好吧
All right.
我覺得 這確實是一個變態酒店
Yeah. I think it's some sort of pervert hotel.
那孩子告訴我 他會把人們幹的那些事錄下來
The kid told me, he films people doing whatnot...
然後寄給他的老闆們看
and sends it to his bosses.
他的老闆們是誰
Who are his bosses?
可能是這家酒店的主人吧 我也不清楚
People who own the hotel. I don't know.
這很重要嗎
Does it really matter?
也許吧
Maybe.
然後呢 他就自己住的把這些都給你說了是吧
And what, he just offered this up to you, did he? Hmm?
我覺得他是想告解
I think he was trying to confess.
這樣啊
Oh.
我覺得他壓力太大了
I think it's been weighing on him.
所以他現在想要悔改
I think he's trying to confess right now...
因為他知道這件事情會如何發酵
because he knows how this is gonna go...
他很怕他的靈魂會無處安放
and he fears for his soul.
嘿 夥計
Hey, buddy. Uh...
如果你真的特別擔心你的靈魂的話
Listen, if you're so worried about your soul...
你從一開始就不應該
maybe you shouldn't have been doing
幹這些壞事
all this bad shit in the first place.
這是我想的那個東西嗎
Is that who I think it is?
我也想看
I wanna see.
等一下
Now, wait a second.
什麼樣的神父
What's a man of God like yourself
會在口袋裡裝著這個
doing with this in his coat?
這不過是人們在做愛嘛
It's just people fuckin'.
不對 你仔細看看 羅斯
No. You take a closer look, Rose.
等等 我認識他
Wait, I know him.
是啊
Uh-huh.
他死了
He's dead.
沒錯
That he is.
他是死了
好吧
All right.
這錢從哪裡來的
Where's the money come from?
這錢...
Well, that money...
我現在沒問你 神父
I ain't asking you right now, Father.
達琳·斯維特女士 錢是從哪裡來的呢
Ms. Darlene Sweet, where's the money come from, hmm?
是我的
It's mine.
你的嗎
It's yours?
真的嗎
Really?
像你這樣的女孩
Where's a girl like you
從哪裡能得到這麼多錢呢
get all this kind of money from, huh?
我自己掙的
I earned it.
唱歌掙的
Singing.
那麼 你一定是個厲害的歌手啊
Well, you must be one hell of a singer then.
是的
I am.
好吧 到你了
All right, your turn.
這些錢到底哪裡來的呀
Where's the money from? Hmm?
她說的是真的
She's telling you the truth.
這些錢都是她的 是她唱歌掙的
That's her money, she earned it singing.
好 你是個神職人員 對吧
Yeah, and you're a man of the cloth, huh?
對
I am.
我忘了告訴你...
You know, I forgot to mention...
我討厭神父
I hate priests.
你要改自己的口供嗎
You wanna change your story?
不
Nope.
那好的吧
Alright then.
小靴子 你為什麼不去用那個唱片機
Boots, why don't you find something
給咱們放點音樂呢
to listen to on that there jukebox?
你不覺得這裡太安靜了嗎
It's too quiet in here, don't you think? Huh?
讓我毛骨悚然
Gives me the willies.
這是誰的歌
Who is this?
深紫樂隊吧 可能
It's Deep Purple, I think.
這風格不大適合我
It's not for me.
現在 我希望你們倆最好
Now, I want you two to pay
對接下來要發生的事情 打起精神來 好嗎
real close attention to what happens next, okay?
我問你問題的時候
And keep it right up there in the front of your minds...
記得集中精神來回答
when I'm asking questions
尋找最真實的答案 明白嗎
looking for truthful answers, okay?
好了
All right.
艾米莉
Emily.
挑個顏色
Pick a color.
紅色還是黑色
Red or black?
都不要
No.
不要嗎
No?
你這就不太好了
Well, that's just not hardly nice.
我可是給了你一次機會 對吧
I'm offering you a chance here, right?
不管怎麼說
On account of the fact that
我們也算是一家人 是不是
we're practically family, all right?
而且 我認為...
And that's downright
我已經相當仁慈了
charitable of me, considering...
小靴子 你聽到姐姐在幹什麼了嗎
Boots, you hearing what your sister's doing?
如果比利·李給你了一次機會
Em, if Billy Lee is offering you a chance,
我認為你應該抓住它
I think you should take it.
你以為你可以就這樣 帶走我的人
Did you think you could just take what's mine,
然後我就放你們走了嗎
and I wouldn't come a-huntin'?
她不屬於你
She ain't yours.
羅西 你是我的嗎
Rosie, are you mine?
當然
Of course.
在來你之前 這裡沒人使用過暴力
There was no violence till you.
是嗎 也許吧
Yeah, maybe.
也許不是
Maybe not.
但現在已經是這樣了 對嗎
But it's there now, isn't it?
選個顏色 我不會再問第二次了
Pick a color, Em. I ain't asking again.
選個顏色
Pick a color.
紅
Red.
那麼你就是黑色了 小服務員
I guess that makes you black, altar boy.
什麼 不 不 不
What? No, no, no.
過來 你現在可以祈禱了
Come here. You got some prayers, you can say 'em now.
原諒我 神父 我罪孽深重
Forgive me, Father, for I have sinned.
我做過比你想的要更糟的事
I have done so much worse than you know.
孩子...
Kid...
弗林神父 我犯了罪 但我悔改了
Father Flynn, I have sinned and I repent.
原諒我 神父
Forgive me, Father.
我有罪 我...
I have sinned and I...
弗林神父 求您了
Father Flynn, please!
你要自己告訴他 或者還是我來說
Do you want to tell him or you want me to do it?
我有罪 但我悔改了
I have sinned and I repent!
米爾斯
Miles...
求您了
Please!
原諒我 神父
Forgive me, Father!
他他媽的才不是什麼神父 孩子
He's not a fucking priest, kid!
好吧 看起來主還沒有寬恕你
Well, it looks like the Lord hasn't forsaken you yet.
不
No!
現在 誰想玩下一輪
Now then, who wants to play next?
哇哦 韋德 安娜貝拉
Ah, whoa, Wade, Annabell...
仔細看好了
keep a close eye there.
看 每個人都變得緊張兮兮的
See, everyone's liable to get a little more squirrelly
現在他們知道 賭注是什麼了
now they know the stakes.
你們倆願意再多說一點細節嗎
You two gonna be more forthcoming?
當然
Sure.
我能來點兒威士卡嗎
Could I have some of that whiskey?
當然 為什麼不呢
Yeah, sure. Why not?
小靴子 請你給神父倒一杯好嗎
Boots, can you pour the padre a glass, please?
我受不了了
I can't do it anymore.
我受不…
I can't...
嘿 小孩
Hey, kid...
如果你他媽的再不閉上嘴
if you don't shut the fuck up,
你就得再玩一輪遊戲
I'm gonna make you play the game again.
讓我們再來一遍
So, let's try this again.
錢是從哪兒來的
Where's the money from?
我偷來的
I stole it...
大概十年前
about a decade ago.
我把它藏在這裡很久
I hid it here, did some time...
幾天前我出去了
got out a few days ago...
今晚回來取走它
came back tonight to retrieve it.
那你為什麼打扮成神父的樣子
Why you dressed up like a priest, then?
這樣我就不用回答太多問題
Didn't want too many questions.
打扮成神父那樣
People tend to look the other way
人們往往會別過頭去
when you're wearin' a collar.
那你呢
And you?
我...
Um...
我只是個歌手
I'm just a singer.
這筆錢碰巧被藏在了我的房間
The money happened to be hidden in my room.
他說如果我幫他拿回這筆錢
He said he would split it...
他會和我分贓
if I could help him get it back.
他當然會這麼說了 當然了
Of course he did. Of course he did.
因為
Yeah, yeah.
因為拿到那些錢根本不是他真正的目的
'Cause that ain't even the real score,
是吧 神父
is it, padre, huh?
因為你找到了這個
'Cause you found this.
我敢說他根本沒告訴你膠捲的事 是吧
I bet you he didn't even tell you about this, did he?
你就不想知道 膠捲裡錄的誰嗎
Huh? Don't you even wanna see who's in it?
不
No.
那不重要
It doesn't matter.
不 親愛的
Oh, no. Then, darlin',
你根本不明白膠捲裡有什麼
you ain't understanding what's on this film.
讓我猜猜
Let me guess.
是...
Um...
是一個
It's some man...
喜歡高談闊論的
who talks...
男人
a lot.
他說的話太多
He talks so much
以至於他以為 他有某種信仰
that he thinks he believes in something.
以及
And really just...
他可以想上誰就上誰
wants to fuck who he wants to fuck.
這種事我看得太多了
I've seen it enough.
甚至看到時都不再感到憤怒
I'm not even mad about it anymore.
我只是...
I'm just...
感到疲累了
tired.
我只是厭煩了
I'm just bored.
你這樣的男人
Of men like you.
你認為我看不出你是什麼樣的人嗎
You think I don't see you for who you really are?
一個內心脆弱的小人罷了
A fragile little man.
只尋找弱小的或迷途的獵物
Preying on the weak and lost.
是 如果我...
Yeah, well, if I...
我知道這膠捲的事
I've heard it.
但我不在乎
And I don't care.
我寧願置身事外 靜觀其變
I'd rather sit here and listen to the rain.
隨你的便吧
You go right ahead.
找到膠捲之後
Why didn't you just leave
你為什麼不走
when you had the film?
這玩意可比幾袋子錢值錢多了
It's worth way more than some bag of money.
我為這些錢花了很多心思
I did time for that money.
我的兄弟 他因為這些失去了生命 這些錢是我的
My brother, he died for that money. That money's mine.
不 這錢是我們的
That money's ours.
這錢是我們的
那膠捲究竟為什麼那麼重要
Why is that film worth so much anyway?
膠捲裡的人已經死了 誰會關心
Guy's dead. Who cares?
是這樣的 小靴子
Well, Boots...
有時候 關於一個人的記憶
sometimes the memory of a man
比他這個人本身重要多了
matters more than the man himself.
我說的對嗎 神父
Ain't that right, padre?
如果你要這麼說的話 是的
Yeah, if you say so.
還有誰會來找這筆錢
Who's gonna come looking for their money?
沒有了
Nobody.
我覺得一直有人在找這筆錢
Somebody's always looking for money!
沒有了 他們都死了 只剩下我了
No, they're all gone. Except me.
你到底是誰
And who are you exactly?
你的故事究竟有幾分可信
Let's just say I wanna check this story out.
神父 你的真名叫什麼
What's your real name, Father?
我叫...
It's, uh...
我告訴過你我真名嗎
Did I tell you my real name?
你從沒有說過
You never did. No.
真的嗎
Oh, really?
現在你又想
Now you wanna
開始跟我玩遊戲了嗎
Start playing games again?
他不記得了
He can't remember.
他的精神不太集中
His mind's not all there.
這是他告訴你的
That's what he told you?
是的
He did.
你相信這個老騙子說的一切嗎
And you believe anything this old crook says?
是的 我相信
I believe that much. Yeah.
好 好
All right, all right.
讓我看看我們能不能喚起他的記憶 達琳
Let's see if we can't jog his memory, huh, Darlene?
選個顏色
Pick a color.
現在又安靜下來了
Now it's quiet again.
我感覺不太妙
I don't like it.
我也感覺不太對
No, I don't like it either.
嘿 你不是會唱歌麼
Hey, ain't you supposed to be a singer? Huh?
不如你唱首歌給我們聽聽吧 達琳
Why don't you sing something for us, Darlene.
不了吧
No, thank you.
我跟你說
Hell, I'll tell you what.
你唱首歌給大家聽聽
If you sing something for us
如果你唱的真的像你自己說的那樣好聽
and if you're as good as you say you are...
我就不逼你玩這遊戲了
I won't make you play the game.
別聽他的
Don't do it.
不管你唱不唱 他還是會繼續那樣做
He's gonna do what he's gonna do,
他可不配聽你唱歌
but he don't deserve to hear you sing.
信不信隨你們的便
Suit your fucking selves!
慢著
Wait...
我聽過更好的
I've heard better.
不 你會傷到比利的
No! You'll hit Billy Lee!
不 我做不到
No, I can't do it.
我做不到
I can't do it no more.
-不 我做不到 -米爾斯
- I can't. I can't do it. - Miles.
我不能再殺人了
I can't kill no more people.
米爾斯
Miles!
幫幫我們
Help us.
我不能再殺人了
I can't kill no more people.
米爾斯 你殺了多少人
How many people have you killed, Miles?
123個
123.
回憶
我的天啊 琴吉 看看這孩子多棒
My heavens, Ginger! Look what your boy can do.
米爾斯 為什麼不繼續開槍了
Miller! Why the fuck have you stopped shooting?
米爾斯
Miles.
我做不到
I can't do it.
我不能再殺人了
I can't kill no more people.
米爾斯
Miles...
沒事
It's all right.
你不需要再殺人了
You don't have to kill any more people.
狗娘養的
Motherfucker!
讓我們看看 你能不能記起這個
Let's see if you can't remember this.
當心點 小服務員
Easy there, altar boy...
拿著槍
Take the gun.
對不起
I'm sorry.
非常對不起
I'm so sorry.
不
No!
幫幫他
Help him.
我做不到
I can't.
不 上帝 求求您了
No, God. No, God, please.
幫幫他
Help him.
求您了 上帝
Please, God.
我不想
I don't wanna...
懺悔吧
Confess.
懺悔吧 孩子
My son, confess.
你不是
You're not a...
你不是神父
You're not a priest.
我當然是
Of course I am.
米爾斯 米爾斯 吾名神父丹尼爾·弗林
Miles Miller, my name is Father Daniel Flynn...
我來這 是為了免除你的罪行
and I'm here to absolve you of your sins.
保佑我 神父 我罪孽深重
Bless me, Father, for I have sinned.
好
Yes.
我有罪
I've sinned.
我犯下的罪行 數不勝數
I've sinned more times than I can count.
我殺過人
I've killed.
我殺過很多人
I've killed so many people.
我很抱歉 神父
I'm so sorry, Father.
沒關係的
It's all right.
不 有關係
No, it's not.
我做了那麼多錯事
I did so much bad.
我說謊 我偷東西
I lied. I stole.
我傷害過別人
I hurt people.
儘管我知道是錯的 我還是做了
I did it all even though I know it was wrong.
我很抱歉 神父
I'm so sorry, Father.
你想免除你的罪行嗎
Do you seek absolution for your sins?
是的
Yes, I do.
你願意將自己 獻給仁慈的主嗎
Do you give yourself to the mercy of the Lord?
是的
Yes.
你願意把你剩下的時間 留給主嗎
Will you give to Him the time that you have left?
對我來說太遲了
I'm too late.
不
No.
永遠都不會遲
It's never too late.
好的 我會試試
Yes. I will try.
我會試著做得更好
I'll try to be better.
我會試著成為一個更好的人
I'll try to be a better man.
我懺悔
I repent.
弗林神父 我懺悔
Father Flynn, I repent.
你被寬恕了
You are forgiven.
米爾斯 米爾斯
Miles Miller.
以聖父
In the name of the Father,
聖子及聖靈之名
the Son, and the Holy Spirit...
你被寬恕了
you are forgiven.
里諾
祝你們好運 各位
Good luck, everyone.
還有47
And 47.
現在 今晚我們請來了一位特別來賓
Now, we have got a special treat for you tonight.
她從美麗的加州洛杉磯
Coming to you all the way
遠道而來
from beautiful Los Angeles, California...
女士們先生們 讓我們用里諾最熱情的方式
Ladies and gentlemen, let's give a warm Reno welcome
歡迎達琳·斯維特
to Darlene Sweet.
感謝你們今晚來聽我的演出
Thank y'all for coming to listen to me tonight.
這對我很重要
It means a lot to me.
皇家酒店謀殺案
謝謝 非常感謝
Thank you. Thank you so much.
你真是太客氣了 謝謝你
That's very kind of you. Thank you.
天呐 快進來 這裡的位子夠我們坐了
God, come on in. There's enough room for everyone.
快進來
Come on in.
現在 可以的話
Now, if it's all right with you...
我們想給你們再演唱幾首
we'd like to do a few more for you now.